[
    {
        "Category": "Room Types",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Availability",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Check-in Date,Check-out Date,Number of Guests",
        "Question": "Can you please tell if there are any rooms available for next weekend?",
        "Sample Answer": "Thank you for considering Taj hotel for your upcoming stay. To better assist you, could you kindly provide the specific dates you would like to check-in and check-out? "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Room Types",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Availability",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Number of Guests,Check-out date",
        "Question": "Can you check if there are any rooms available for 15 March?",
        "Sample Answer": "I've checked our availability for {Date}, and I'm pleased to inform you that we do have rooms available for that date. If you'd like to proceed with booking, please let me know, and I'll be happy to assist you further."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Room Types",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Availability",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Number of Guests,Check-out date",
        "Question": "Can you check if there are any rooms available for 15 March?",
        "Sample Answer": "I've checked our availability for {Date}, and I'm sorry to inform you that we do not have rooms available for those dates. We have rooms available on {Date} and {Date}, though.\" Incase you plan to travel early or later."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Payments",
        "Sub Category": "Requests",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Payment/offer",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Guest Identification,Time Frame,Email Address",
        "Question": "Can you send the invoice for my last stay to my email?",
        "Sample Answer": "To send an invoice to your email, we'll need to confirm your booking details. Please provide your room number or phone number and dates of stay."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Payments",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Payment/offer",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Booking Information",
        "Question": "How can I review the charges made to my room during my stay?",
        "Sample Answer": "To review detailed billing information, please provide your phone number and the name your room was booked under."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Cancel/Refund",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Booking Details",
        "Question": "Can I cancel my booking?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, booking cancellation is allowed 24-48 hours before check-in. Please inform us within this time frame if you wish to cancel your booking."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Cancel/Refund",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Booking Details",
        "Question": "Will I get full refund on my cancellation?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, you will receive a full refund if canceled before 72 hours of check-in, a 50% refund if canceled before 48 hours of check-in, and a 20% refund if canceled less than 24 hours before check-in."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Customer Account",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Customer Account ",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Booking Details",
        "Question": "What's the status of my refund request for the canceled booking?",
        "Sample Answer": "For refund status, we need your booking ID and the name under which the reservation was made to retrieve the information."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Feedback",
        "Sub Category": "Instructions",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Feedback",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Booking Details,Specific Incident Details",
        "Question": "How do I log a complaint about the room service I received?",
        "Sample Answer": "To log a complaint, please provide us with your room number, the date of the incident, and a brief description of the issue."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Reservations",
        "Sub Category": "Instructions",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Reservation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Reservation Details,New check-in date,New check-out date",
        "Question": "I need to change the dates of my reservation. How can I do that?",
        "Sample Answer": "To change your reservation dates, please provide your booking ID and the new dates you're requesting."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "Requests",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Event/Activity",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Type of Surprise,Date of surprise,Room Reservation Details,Personalization",
        "Question": "Can I have a surprise arrangement made for my partner's birthday?",
        "Sample Answer": "For special arrangements, please provide details about your request, and we'll do our best to accommodate it."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Customer Account",
        "Sub Category": "Issues",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Customer Account ",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Reservation Details,Account details",
        "Question": "Why are all my future reservations not listed on my reservations list?",
        "Sample Answer": "I'm sorry to hear about the trouble with your reservations not appearing on your list. \nThere could be several reasons for this discrepancy, such as technical issues, data synchronization delays, or discrepancies in the reservation process. \nTo address this promptly, I recommend reaching out to our customer support team with your account details and reservation information. They'll be able to investigate the matter thoroughly and provide you with a resolution."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Checkout/check in",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Check In/Check Out",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What are the check-in and check-out times?",
        "Sample Answer": "Check-in is at 1 PM, and check-out is at 11 AM. Early check-in or late check-out can be arranged based on availability."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "Instructions",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "How can I access the hotel Wi-Fi?",
        "Sample Answer": "Wi-Fi is available throughout the hotel and is complimentary. To access the Wi-Fi, connect to 'HotelGuest' network and use the provided password. If no password was provided, you can use your phone number as the password."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Parking",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Vehicle Information,Booking details ",
        "Question": "Is parking available at the hotel?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we offer on-site parking on a first-come, first-served basis for a daily rate of [insert rate]."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Room Types",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Booking details",
        "Question": "Can I request an extra bed or crib in my room?",
        "Sample Answer": "We can provide an extra bed or crib upon request, subject to availability. There may be an additional charge for an extra bed."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Pet details ",
        "Question": "Are pets allowed in the hotel?",
        "Sample Answer": "Pets are welcome with prior notice and a fee of [insert fee] per stay. Please refer to our pet policy for details."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Pet Details",
        "Question": "Are pets allowed in the hotel?",
        "Sample Answer": "Sorry, our hotel is not pet-friendly, so pets are not allowed. Please refer to our pet policy for details."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Do you offer laundry services?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we offer laundry and dry cleaning services at a rate of [insert rate]. Items given before [insert time] will be returned the same day."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Policies",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What are some must-see attractions nearby?",
        "Sample Answer": "Our city has many attractions to offer. Our reception team can provide you with a map and recommendations."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Transportation",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Transportation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Mode of Transportation Preference",
        "Question": "How can I get to the city center from the hotel?",
        "Sample Answer": "You can take the [insert public transport options], or we can arrange a taxi for you. The city center is [insert distance] away."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is room service available and at what times?",
        "Sample Answer": "Room service is available from [insert hours], offering a selection of dishes from our in-house menu."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What are the hours for the fitness center?",
        "Sample Answer": "Our fitness center is open from [insert hours] and is accessible with your room key."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Policies",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What is the hotel's smoking policy?",
        "Sample Answer": "Our hotel is entirely non-smoking. Smoking is permitted in designated outdoor areas only."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Do you offer spa services?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, our spa offers a range of services including massages and treatments. The spa is open from [insert hours]. Please note that these services are chargeable."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Checkout/check in",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Check In/Check Out",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Check-in Date,Arrival Time",
        "Question": "Can I check in early if I arrive before the standard check-in time?",
        "Sample Answer": "Early check-in is subject to availability. Please contact us in advance and we'll do our best to accommodate your request."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Room Types",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Room type",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Check-in and Check-out Dates,Number of Guests",
        "Question": "What room types do you have available (e.g., single, double, suite)?",
        "Sample Answer": "We offer a variety of room types to cater to different preferences and needs. Our available room types typically include: classic, executive, superior and suite room types."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Room Types",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Room type",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Dates of Stay,Number of Guests",
        "Question": "What is the rate for Superior Room?",
        "Sample Answer": "Currently, the rate for our Superior Room starts at (?rate) per night. However, rates may vary depending on factors such as the date of stay, length of stay, and any special promotions or discounts available."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Reservations",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Payment/offer",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Preferred Dates",
        "Question": "Do you offer any special packages or discounts for [specific occasions]?",
        "Sample Answer": "We offer special packages and discounts for specific occasions. Please inquire about the occasion you have in mind for more details."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Reservations",
        "Sub Category": "Instructions",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Reservation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "How can I make a reservation?",
        "Sample Answer": "You can make a reservation by calling our reservation desk at [phone number] or by emailing us at [email address]."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Reservations",
        "Sub Category": "Instructions",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Reservation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Can I book a room online, or do I need to call/email?",
        "Sample Answer": "You can book a room online through our website, or you can call/email our reservation desk for assistance."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Checkout/check in",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Check In/Check Out",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Desired Time",
        "Question": "Is early check-in or late check-out available, and is there an additional fee?",
        "Sample Answer": "Early check-in and late check-out may be available, with potential additional fees."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Reservations",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Cancel/Refund",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What is your cancellation policy?",
        "Sample Answer": "Our cancellation policy allows for free cancellation until 2 PM, three days prior to your scheduled arrival. Cancellations made after this time will incur a penalty equivalent to one night's charge, in addition to any applicable taxes and fees."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Reservations",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Cancel/Refund",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is there a penalty for cancelling or changing my reservation?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, there is a penalty for cancelling or changing your reservation. Cancellations or changes made after the specified deadline may result in a penalty charge equivalent to one night's stay, plus any applicable taxes and fees."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Parking",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Do you have onsite parking, and is there a fee?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we do offer onsite parking for our guests, and the best part is there is no fee for parking! You're welcome to park your vehicle securely during your stay without any additional charges"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Transportation",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Transportation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Date and Time,Location,Number of Passengers,Date and Time",
        "Question": "Is there cab service to/from the airport or other locations?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we provide cab/car services to and from the airport, as well as other selected locations. Our shuttle service is meticulously designed to offer our guests convenient transportation options. Please note that this service iis chargeable"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Attractions",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Interests",
        "Question": "Do you have information about tours or activities in the area?",
        "Sample Answer": "We have a wealth of information about tours and activities in the area to help make your stay even more enjoyable. Depending on your interests, we can provide recommendations for various attractions, excursions, and local experiences. For more information please contact our front desk."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Room Types",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Room type",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Room Preference,Check-in/check-out Date",
        "Question": "Can I request a specific view or room location?",
        "Sample Answer": "We understand that preferences for views or room locations can enhance your overall experience during your stay. While we cannot guarantee specific requests, we always strive to accommodate our guests' preferences to the best of our ability, subject to availability."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Payments",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Payment/offer",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What forms of payment do you accept?",
        "Sample Answer": "We offer flexibility in payment methods to cater to our guests' preferences, accepting various forms such as credit cards, debit cards, and cash. However, please note that a small booking amount is required before your stay to reserve a room"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Payments",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Payment/offer",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Can I pay with a credit card or cash upon arrival?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, you can pay with a credit card or cash upon arrival. However, please note that a small booking amount is required before your stay to reserve a room"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Accessible",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Specific Needs,Type of Facilities",
        "Question": "Are your facilities accessible for guests with disabilities?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, absolutely. We are committed to ensuring that all of our guests, including those with disabilities, have a comfortable and accessible stay with us."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Room Types",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Accessible",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Check-in/check-out Date,Specific Accessibility Needs",
        "Question": "Do you have rooms equipped with accessibility features?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we do have rooms equipped with accessibility features to accommodate guests with special needs. "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Attractions",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Tour Package Details",
        "Question": "Which attractions will I visit with Private Taj Mahal Tour from Delhi by Car?",
        "Sample Answer": "The Private Taj Mahal Tour from Delhi by Car includes visits to various attractions around the Taj Mahal."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Transportation",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Transportation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Which company provides Private Taj Mahal Tour from Delhi by Car?",
        "Sample Answer": "One reputable company that offers Private Taj Mahal Tours from Delhi by car is \"Viator.\" They collaborate with local tour operators to provide private tours tailored to your preferences, including transportation from Delhi to the Taj Mahal and back."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Duration of Storage,Type of Storage Needed",
        "Question": "Do you have storage facilities for suitcases? ",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we offer luggage storage facilities for our guests. You can store your luggage for a duration of 6 to 10 hours after check-out time. Please note that fees may apply for this service."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Room Types",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Room type",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Where can I find room descriptions?",
        "Sample Answer": "Room descriptions can be found on our website or provided upon request."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Reservations",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Payment/offer",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Corporate Identification",
        "Question": "Can I get my corporate rate when making a reservation online?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, you can usually get your corporate rate when making a reservation online, provided you enter the appropriate corporate "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Reservations",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Reservation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Check-in and Check-out Dates,Number of Rooms",
        "Question": "Can I book more than one room at a time?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, you can typically book more than one room at a time, depending on availability and the hotel's booking policies."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Reservations",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Availability",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "How will I know if the room I've selected is available?",
        "Sample Answer": "You will typically be informed of room availability during the online booking process. Alternatively, you can contact the hotel directly to confirm availability."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Room type",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Will I be guaranteed that my room will have the bed type, view or location I requested?",
        "Sample Answer": "While hotels strive to accommodate preferences, they cannot always guarantee specific bed types, views, or locations."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Reservations",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Reservation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "How old must I be to reserve a room?",
        "Sample Answer": "The minimum age requirement to reserve a room varies by hotel but is typically over 18 or 21 years old."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Payments",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Payment/offer",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Can I pay for another guest's room (a friend, family member or co-worker, etc.) with my credit card?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, you can pay for another guest's room with your credit card, provided you provide authorization."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Payments",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Payment/offer",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What is a third-party credit card authorization?",
        "Sample Answer": "A third-party credit card authorization allows someone other than the cardholder to pay for the reservation."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Payments",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Payment",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Do I need to send a credit card authorization for multiple rooms at the same hotel that are being billed to the same credit card?",
        "Sample Answer": "It depends on the hotel's policy. Some may require a credit card authorization form for multiple rooms billed to the same credit card."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Checkout/check in",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Payment/offer",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What type of identification must guests present at check-in if a third party is paying for the guest room?",
        "Sample Answer": "Guests typically need to present a valid ID at check-in, especially if a third party is paying for the room."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Reservations",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Reservation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Will I receive a confirmation of my reservation?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, you should receive a confirmation of your reservation via email or text."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Reservations",
        "Sub Category": "Instructions",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Reservation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "How can I review and/or modify my reservation after it has been made?",
        "Sample Answer": "You can typically review and modify your reservation online through the hotel's website or by contacting us directly."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "front Desk",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Where can I find more information about hotel?",
        "Sample Answer": "For more information about the hotel, you can visit our website, contact us directly, or check online review platforms."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Reservations",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Cancel/Refund",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "If I cancel or change my reservation, will I get a refund or credit? Will I have to pay any fees?",
        "Sample Answer": "Our cancellation and reservation change policies vary depending on the specific terms of your booking, including the room type, rate plan, and any applicable promotions. "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Checkout/check in",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Check In/Check Out",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Will I be charged a night's stay if I arrive late or miss my arrival date?",
        "Sample Answer": "Typically, if you arrive late or miss your scheduled arrival date without canceling your reservation in advance, you may still be charged for the first night's stay."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Reservations",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Payment/offer",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Reservation Status,Claim Details",
        "Question": "Do I need a reservation confirmed to submit a claim?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, typically a reservation needs to be confirmed before submitting a claim. Having a confirmed reservation allows us to verify the details of your booking and ensure that any claim submitted is valid and applicable."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Feedback",
        "Sub Category": "Instructions",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Feedback",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Where do I send questions and comments about thie hotels?",
        "Sample Answer": "If you have any questions or comments about the hotel, please feel free to send them to our customer support team. You can typically find contact information, such as an email address or contact form, on the website's \"Contact Us\" or \"Support\" page. "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "front Desk",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "How can I contact Hotel Guest Care Support?",
        "Sample Answer": "To contact Hotel Guest Care Support, you can typically find their contact information on the hotel's official website or your booking confirmation. "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Restaurants",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Kitchen",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Meal Preferences",
        "Question": "What food & drink options are available ?",
        "Sample Answer": "Certainly! Here's a sample menu of our food and drink options:"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Requests",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Attractions",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is Hotel located near the city centre?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, our hotel is conveniently located near the city center. "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Event/Activity",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Duration of Stay,Specific Interests or Needs",
        "Question": "What are the hotel facilities for children 4 to 6 years old? Like kid club, mini zoo etc",
        "Sample Answer": "For children aged 4 to 6 years old, we offer a range of exciting and engaging facilities to ensure they have a memorable and enjoyable stay:Kids Club,Outdoor Play Area,Children's Pool and Kids' Activities."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "The swimming pool is heated or not?",
        "Sample Answer": "Our swimming pool is (yes or no) heated for our guests. Whether you're looking to take a refreshing dip or simply relax poolside, you can rest assured that our pool provides a pleasant and inviting environment year-round. "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Attractions",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Specific Interests,Distance Range",
        "Question": "What is nearby? Is anything walking distance?",
        "Sample Answer": "We're conveniently located near a variety of attractions and amenities, with some within walking distance. Depending on your interests, you'll find a range of options to explore nearby."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Transportation",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Transportation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Check-out Dates",
        "Question": "Does the hotel provide return airport transfer? If yes, what are the charges?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we do provide return airport transfer services for our guests' convenience. The charges for the return airport transfer depend on various factors such as the type of vehicle requested, and any additional services required."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Room Types",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Room type",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Number of Guests and Room Type Preference,Dates and Duration of Stay",
        "Question": "Hi, do you have any rooms with twin beds and could 3 adults stay in one suite?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we do have rooms available with twin beds. Regarding accommodating three adults in one suite, it's possible, but additional charges may apply for the extra guest."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Can you provide any information on what is in your gym?",
        "Sample Answer": "Our gym facilities include state-of-the-art equipment for cardio, strength training, and fitness classes. You can enjoy amenities such as treadmills, weights, and yoga mats."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Restaurants/Club",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is there a club lounge access with free drinks and snacks available?",
        "Sample Answer": "We offer club lounge access with complimentary drinks and snacks for eligible guests. Please inquire about the availability of this service when making your reservation."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are all guests free to attend yoga classes?",
        "Sample Answer": "All guests are welcome to attend yoga classes, usually offered as part of our wellness program. Please check our schedule for class timings and availability."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Checkout/check in",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Check In/Check Out",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Booking Details",
        "Question": "Hi, I?m wondering if the late check out is available?",
        "Sample Answer": "Late check-out options are available upon request, subject to availability. Additional charges may apply depending on the time of check-out."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Kitchen",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is there any extra charge for a floating breakfast?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, there may be an extra charge for a floating breakfast. Please check with our staff for pricing and availability when making your reservation."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is Wi-Fi included in the room rate?",
        "Sample Answer": "Wi-Fi is typically included in the room rate, offering complimentary internet access throughout your stay."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What is the Wi-Fi password?",
        "Sample Answer": "The Wi-Fi password is [provide password]."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "How reliable is the Wi-Fi connection?",
        "Sample Answer": "Our Wi-Fi connection is reliable, ensuring seamless internet access for our guests."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there any data limits for the Wi-Fi usage?",
        "Sample Answer": "There are no data limits for Wi-Fi usage; you can browse and stream without restrictions."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Can I connect multiple devices to the Wi-Fi?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, you can connect multiple devices to our Wi-Fi network."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is the Wi-Fi accessible in all areas of the hotel?",
        "Sample Answer": "Wi-Fi is accessible in all areas of the hotel, including rooms, lobby, and common areas."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Do you offer high-speed Wi-Fi?",
        "Sample Answer": "We offer high-speed Wi-Fi to ensure fast and efficient internet access for our guests."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Swimming pool costume is necessary?",
        "Sample Answer": "Swimming pool costume is necessary for all guests using the pool area."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What is the Swimming pool timming?",
        "Sample Answer": "The swimming pool timings are from [insert timings here]."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "At what floor do you swimming allocated?",
        "Sample Answer": "The swimming pool is allocated on the [insert floor here]."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Restaurants/Club",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is Stag entry allowed in club?",
        "Sample Answer": "Stag entry is allowed in the club, and charges may vary depending on the day and club policies."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Restaurants/Club",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What are the charges of stag entry for hotel Guest?",
        "Sample Answer": "Stag entry charges for hotel guests can be obtained from the front desk or club reception."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Restaurants/Club",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is couple entry free for club?",
        "Sample Answer": "Couple entry to the club may be complimentary for hotel guests, subject to club policies and any special offers."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Restaurants/Club",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What are the charges for outsider?",
        "Sample Answer": "The charges for outsiders for club entry vary depending on the club's policies and any ongoing promotions."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Restaurants/Club",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Check-in/check-out Dates",
        "Question": "Do hotel guests gets any Special offer for club entry ?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, hotel guests often receive special offers or discounts for club entry. These offers may vary depending on the hotel's partnership with the club and any ongoing promotions."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Restaurants/Club",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What time does the club Close?",
        "Sample Answer": "The club closes at [insert closing time]."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What time are the yoga classes offered?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yoga classes are offered at 8:00 AM and 5:00 PM daily."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Do I need to pre-book the yoga sessions?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, pre-booking for yoga sessions is required."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are the yoga classes suitable for beginners?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, the yoga classes are suitable for beginners."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is there an additional fee for the yoga classes?",
        "Sample Answer": "No, yoga classes are included in your stay."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Do you provide yoga mats for the classes?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yoga mats are usually provided for the classes, but guests are welcome to bring their own if preferred."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "How long do the yoga sessions typically last?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yoga sessions typically last for one hour."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are the yoga classes held indoors or outdoors?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yoga classes may be held indoors or outdoors, depending on weather conditions and venue availability"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is there a certified instructor leading the yoga sessions?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, there is a certified instructor leading the sessions."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Date and Time Preferences",
        "Question": "Are private yoga sessions available upon request?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, private yoga sessions are available upon request."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there any specific attire requirements for the yoga classes?",
        "Sample Answer": "Comfortable workout attire is recommended for yoga classes."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Restaurants/Club",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What time does the club open?",
        "Sample Answer": "The club typically opens in the evening, usually around 8:00 PM, but exact opening times may vary depending on the day of the week and any special events."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Restaurants/Club",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is there a cover charge for the club?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, there is a cover charge for entry to the club. The amount of the cover charge may vary depending on factors such as the day of the week, special events, or promotions. "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Restaurants/Club",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Can I reserve a table in the club?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, you can reserve a table by calling our reservations line."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Restaurants/Club",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there any special events happening at the club tonight?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, tonight at the club, we're hosting a live DJ performance featuring renowned DJ Spinmaster! Join us for an unforgettable night of music, dancing, and cocktails. "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Restaurants/Club",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Na",
        "Question": "Do you offer bottle service in the club?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we do offer bottle service in the club for guests looking to elevate their experience and enjoy VIP treatment."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Restaurants/Club",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is there a dress code for the club?",
        "Sample Answer": "We do have a dress code for the club to maintain a stylish and upscale atmosphere. Smart casual attire is generally recommended, with no athletic wear, beachwear, or excessively casual clothing permitted."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Restaurants/Club",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there any age restrictions for entry to the club?",
        "Sample Answer": "There are age restrictions for entry to the club; guests must be at least 21 years old with valid identification to enter and enjoy the club's offerings. "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Restaurants/Club",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Can I bring guests who are not staying at the hotel to the club?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, you can bring guests who are not staying at the hotel to the club, although entry policies may apply, such as guest fees or age restrictions. "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Restaurants/Club",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is there parking available for club patrons?",
        "Sample Answer": "Parking is typically available for club patrons; however, availability may vary depending on the hotel's parking facilities and any event or local restrictions. "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Event/Activity",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Preferences(time,languages,age range,etc)",
        "Question": "Does the hotel offer babysitting services?",
        "Sample Answer": "The hotel may offer babysitting services upon request, subject to availability and additional charges."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Event/Activity",
        "Information Required From Client ": "check-in/check-out date",
        "Question": "Are there any children's play areas or activities available?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, there are children's play areas and activities available."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Event/Activity",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Check-in and Check-out Dates,booking informations",
        "Question": "Do you provide cribs or baby cots for infants?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we provide cribs or baby cots for infants upon request to ensure a comfortable stay for your little ones."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Restaurants",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Event/Activity",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Na",
        "Question": "Are there any family-friendly dining options onsite?",
        "Sample Answer": "Absolutely, we offer family-friendly dining options onsite, including kid's menus and high chairs, to cater to the whole family's needs."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Event/Activity",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Duration of Rental,Specific Requirements",
        "Question": "Can I rent strollers or other baby equipment from the hotel?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, you can rent strollers or other baby equipment from the hotel to make your stay more convenient and enjoyable."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Event/Activity",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there any swimming pools specifically for children?",
        "Sample Answer": "We have swimming pools specifically designed for children, offering a safe and fun environment for them to splash around and have a great time."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Event/Activity",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Booking Details",
        "Question": "Do you have any special events or programs for kids during our stay?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we have special events and programs for kids during your stay."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Event/Activity",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Interests and Preferences",
        "Question": "Are there any nearby attractions suitable for families with children?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, there are nearby attractions suitable for families with children."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Event/Activity",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Specific Needs or Preferences",
        "Question": "Can you recommend any childcare services in the area?",
        "Sample Answer": "Certainly! We recommend [Name of Childcare Service], located just [distance] away from our hotel. "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Event/Activity",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there any safety measures in place for children at the hotel?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we prioritize the safety of all our guests, including children, and have various safety measures in place. "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Parking",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Na",
        "Question": "Is valet parking offered?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we provide valet parking services for guests who prefer the added convenience of valet"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Parking",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there any parking restrictions?",
        "Sample Answer": "There are no parking restrictions for guests; however, please park in designated areas to ensure smooth traffic flow."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Parking",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is there a designated area for oversized vehicles?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we have a designated area for oversized vehicles to accommodate larger vehicles comfortably."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Parking",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is the parking area secure?",
        "Sample Answer": "Our parking area is secure, equipped with surveillance cameras and regular patrols to ensure the safety of vehicles parked on-site."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Parking",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there electric vehicle charging stations available?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we do provide electric vehicle charging stations for our guests' convenience."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Parking",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What is the maximum height clearance for the parking garage?",
        "Sample Answer": "The maximum height clearance for the parking garage is [insert height clearance]."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Room Types",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Booking Details",
        "Question": "Do you provide extra beds?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we do provide extra beds upon request. Please let us know your requirements, and we'll be happy to assist you."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Reservation Details",
        "Question": "Is it possible to get a crib for our infant?",
        "Sample Answer": "Certainly! We offer cribs for infants upon request. Please inform us in advance, and we'll ensure one is prepared for your stay"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Room Types",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Reservation Details",
        "Question": "Are extra beds available for our stay?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, extra beds can be provided on a chargeable basis, each room can have one extra-bedding."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Room Types",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Reservation Details",
        "Question": "Can we request an additional bed for our room?",
        "Sample Answer": "Absolutely, you can request an additional bed for your room."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Room Types",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Na",
        "Question": "Are there any charges for requesting an extra bed?",
        "Sample Answer": "Charges for requesting an extra bed may apply depending on the hotel's policies and availability."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Reservations",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Reservation Details",
        "Question": "Can you confirm if a crib is available for our reservation?",
        "Sample Answer": "Certainly, I can confirm if a crib is available for your reservation. May I have your reservation details, please?"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Policies",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Pet details",
        "Question": "Are pets allowed in the hotel?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, pets are allowed in designated areas."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Policies",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Pet details",
        "Question": "What is the pet policy here?",
        "Sample Answer": "We warmly welcome pets at our establishment. However, please note that there may be specific guidelines and restrictions regarding pet size, breed, and additional fees."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Policies",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Pet details",
        "Question": "Are there any restrictions on bringing pets?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we do have restrictions on bringing pets. Please note that only service animals are allowed on the premises, in accordance with our hotel policy and regulations. "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Policies",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is there an additional fee for bringing pets?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, there is typically an additional fee for bringing pets to the hotel."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Policies",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Booking Details,Pet details",
        "Question": "Are there designated areas for pets?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we have designated areas for pets within the hotel premises."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Policies",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there any specific rules for pet owners?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we do have specific rules for pet owners. Pets are typically welcome at our hotel, but there are guidelines to ensure the comfort and safety of all guests"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Policies",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Booking Details,Pet details",
        "Question": "Do you provide any amenities for pets?",
        "Sample Answer": "Certainly! We understand that pets are part of the family, so we offer various amenities to ensure their comfort during their stay. These amenities may include pet beds, bowls, treats, and even pet-friendly room service options. "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Na",
        "Question": "Is laundry service available at the hotel?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, laundry service is available."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What are the laundry service hours?",
        "Sample Answer": "Laundry service hours are from 8:00 AM to 6:00 PM."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Type and Quantity",
        "Question": "How much does it cost to have laundry done?",
        "Sample Answer": "The cost of laundry services varies depending on the type and quantity of items you need laundered. "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Do you offer same-day laundry service?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, same-day laundry service is available upon request."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Can I request express laundry service?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, express laundry service is available with an additional fee."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Do you provide dry cleaning options?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we provide dry cleaning options for delicate items."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there any special instructions for laundry items?",
        "Sample Answer": "Please separate whites from colors and provide any special instructions."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is there a laundry bag provided in the room?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we provide a laundry bag in every room for your convenience. Simply fill it with your laundry items, and our housekeeping staff will take care of the rest."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Do you offer self-service laundry facilities?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, self-service laundry facilities are available on the third floor."
    },
    {
        "Category": "",
        "Sub Category": "",
        "Sub Sub Category": "",
        "Information Required From Client ": "",
        "Question": "Do you offer self-service laundry facilities?",
        "Sample Answer": "No, we do not offer self-service laundry facilities at our establishment. However, we do provide a charged, full-service laundry options where our staff will take care of washing, drying, and folding your clothes for you, ensuring convenience and quality results."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are laundry detergents provided?",
        "Sample Answer": "We do not provide laundry detergents, but we offer comprehensive laundry services for your convenience."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Attractions",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Preferences or Interests,Distance or Mode of Transport",
        "Question": "What are the must-visit landmarks nearby?",
        "Sample Answer": "The Old Town Square with its historic architecture is a must-visit landmark nearby."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Attractions",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there any famous museums or art galleries in the area?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, the City Art Gallery and National Museum showcase renowned works of art. To know more please contact the front desk"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Attractions",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Scenic Preferences",
        "Question": "Can you recommend any scenic walking or hiking trails nearby?",
        "Sample Answer": "Explore the breathtaking trails of Pine Ridge Park for scenic walks and hikes.To know more please contact the front desk"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Restaurants",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Attractions",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Preferences",
        "Question": "What are some popular restaurants or cafes within walking distance?",
        "Sample Answer": "Check out the vibrant eateries on Main Street for popular dining options within walking distance. To know more please contact the front desk"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Attractions",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there any historical sites or monuments worth seeing nearby?",
        "Sample Answer": "Don't miss the impressive Fort Heritage Monument just a short walk away. To know more please contact the front desk"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Attractions",
        "Information Required From Client ": "dates and times",
        "Question": "Do you offer tours to nearby attractions?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we offer guided tours to nearby attractions like the Botanical Gardens and the Castle. To know more please contact the front desk"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Attractions",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Na",
        "Question": "Are there any parks or gardens nearby for a leisurely stroll?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes there is a park/garden nearby for leisurely strolls. To know more please contact the front desk."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Attractions",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Preferences",
        "Question": "Can you recommend any local markets or shopping areas?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes we recommend the Farmer's Market for local produce and unique shopping experiences. To know more please contact the front desk"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Attractions",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there any theaters or cinemas nearby for entertainment?",
        "Sample Answer": "Enjoy entertainment at the nearby (name) Theater showcasing the latest shows and films.To know more please contact the fromnt desk"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Attractions",
        "Information Required From Client ": "time frame",
        "Question": "What outdoor activities are available nearby, like boating or cycling?",
        "Sample Answer": "Nearby lakes offer opportunities for boating and cycling along scenic routes. To know more please contact the fromnt desk"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Attractions",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Preferences",
        "Question": "Are there any family-friendly attractions nearby?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes there are many family friendly attractions nearby. To know more please contact the front desk."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Attractions",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Booking details",
        "Question": "Can you recommend any local festivals or events happening during my stay?",
        "Sample Answer": "Experience the local culture at the annual (name) happening during your stay. To know more please contact the front desk"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Attractions",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Na",
        "Question": "Are there any beaches or waterfront areas nearby?",
        "Sample Answer": "Discover the tranquil beaches of (name) just a short drive away. To know more please contact the fromnt desk"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Attractions",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Can you provide information on any nearby wineries or breweries?",
        "Sample Answer": "Sample exquisite wines at the nearby Vineyard Estate or brewery tours at (name).To know more please contact the fromnt desk"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Local Attractions/Event",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Attractions",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there any sports stadiums or arenas nearby for events or games?",
        "Sample Answer": "Catch exciting games and events at the Sports Arena located nearby."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Transportation",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Transportation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Na",
        "Question": "What transportation options are available from the airport?",
        "Sample Answer": "From the airport, guests can access various transportation options including taxis, ride-sharing services, airport shuttles, and public transportation such as buses or trains."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Transportation",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Transportation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Time for departure and return",
        "Question": "Can you arrange a shuttle service to downtown?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we would be delighted to arrange a shuttle service to downtown for you. Please let us know your desired time for departure and return, and we'll coordinate with our transportation team to accommodate your needs. Additional charges may apply depending on the distance and type of transportation requested."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Transportation",
        "Sub Category": "Recommendations ",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Transportation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is there a nearby subway or metro station?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, there is a nearby subway or metro station located within walking distance from the hotel. It provides convenient access to various attractions and destinations in the city."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Transportation",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Transportation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are taxi services readily available from the hotel?",
        "Sample Answer": "Taxi services are readily available from the hotel; our staff can assist you in arranging transportation as needed."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Transportation",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Transportation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Date and Time,Preferences",
        "Question": "Do you offer car rental services onsite?",
        "Sample Answer": "We do offer car rental services onsite for guests who prefer to explore at their own pace."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Transportation",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Transportation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Date and Time,Preferences",
        "Question": "Are there any bike rental facilities nearby?",
        "Sample Answer": "While we don't have bike rental facilities onsite, there are nearby rental shops where you can easily rent bicycles/bikes to explore the area."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Transportation",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Transportation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "How far is the nearest bus stop?",
        "Sample Answer": "The nearest bus stop is located [insert distance] away from the hotel; our staff can provide directions and assistance in using public transportation."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Transportation",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Transportation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Date and Time,Preferences",
        "Question": "Are there any guided tours or transportation services for local attractions?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we offer guided tours and transportation services for local attractions. Our concierge team can provide information on available tours and help you book transportation for a hassle-free experience."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Transportation",
        "Sub Category": "Requests",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Transportation",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Date and Time,Preferences",
        "Question": "Can you arrange transportation for day trips outside the city?",
        "Sample Answer": "Certainly! We offer transportation arrangements for day trips outside the city. Our concierge can assist you in organizing transportation tailored to your specific needs and preferences."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What time does room service start and end?",
        "Sample Answer": "Room service typically starts at 6:00 AM and ends at 11:00 PM."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Kitchen",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Can I see a menu for room service?",
        "Sample Answer": "Certainly! Our room service menu offers a wide range of delicious options for you to enjoy in the comfort of your room. Unfortunately, I'm unable to display the menu directly here, but you can find it in your room's information booklet "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Kitchen",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there vegetarian options available for room service?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we offer a variety of vegetarian options for room service."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Kitchen",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Do you offer gluten-free options for room service?",
        "Sample Answer": "Absolutely, we provide gluten-free options for room service upon request."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is there an extra charge for room service?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, there's a small additional charge for room service orders."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Na",
        "Question": "How long does room service typically take to arrive?",
        "Sample Answer": "Room service usually arrives within 30-45 minutes of placing your order."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Kitchen",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Can I order alcohol through room service?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, alcohol can typically be ordered through room service, subject to the hotel's policies and local regulations. "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Booking details",
        "Question": "Do you have any specials or promotions for room service?",
        "Sample Answer": "We have ongoing specials and promotions for room service; feel free to inquire about the current offerings."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Kitchen",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Na",
        "Question": "Can I order breakfast through room service?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, you can order breakfast through room service at any time during the breakfast hours."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there any late-night options available for room service?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we offer late-night options for room service until our closing time."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "House Keeping",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Can I order extra towels or amenities through room service?",
        "Sample Answer": "Certainly, you can order extra towels or amenities through room service."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Kitchen",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is there a minimum order requirement for room service?",
        "Sample Answer": "There is no minimum order requirement for room service."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Kitchen",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there any kids' meal options available for room service?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we have kids' meal options available for room service."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Kitchen",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Can I order food from outside the hotel through room service?",
        "Sample Answer": "Unfortunately, we only provide food from our hotel's restaurant for room service."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Kitchen",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there healthy meal options available for room service?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we offer healthy meal options for room service."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Kitchen",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Can I order desserts or snacks through room service?",
        "Sample Answer": "Of course, you can order desserts or snacks through room service."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Do you offer 24-hour room service?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we offer 24-hour room service for our guests."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Can I request specific dietary requirements for room service?",
        "Sample Answer": "Absolutely, we can accommodate specific dietary requirements for room service."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is there a service charge added to room service orders?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, a small service charge is added to room service orders."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Services",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Kitchen",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Can I order room service to the poolside or other areas of the hotel?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, you can order room service to the poolside or any other designated areas of the hotel."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Na",
        "Question": "What are the Fitness Center's opening hours?",
        "Sample Answer": "Fitness Center hours are 6 am to 10 pm daily."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Na",
        "Question": "Is there a fee to use the Fitness Center?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, there's a nominal fee for having access to Fitness Center."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are towels provided in the Fitness Center?",
        "Sample Answer": "Towels are provided for guests using the Fitness Center."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "date and time",
        "Question": "Do you offer personal training sessions?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we offer personal training sessions upon request."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there any age restrictions for using the Fitness Center?",
        "Sample Answer": "The Fitness Center is available to guests aged 18 and above."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Can I access the Fitness Center 24/7?",
        "Sample Answer": "Access to the Fitness Center is available (timing) for hotel guests."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there cardio machines available in the Fitness Center?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, there are various cardio machines available."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Do you have free weights in the Fitness Center?",
        "Sample Answer": "Free weights are available in the Fitness Center."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Fitness",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is there a sauna or steam room in the Fitness Center?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we have both a sauna and steam room."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Policies",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are fitness classes offered in the Fitness Center?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we offer a variety of fitness classes in the Fitness Center."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Policies",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Can I smoke in my room?",
        "Sample Answer": "I'm sorry, but smoking is not permitted in our rooms. However, designated smoking areas are available outside the hotel premises for guests who wish to smoke. "
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Policies",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is smoking allowed in any areas of the hotel?",
        "Sample Answer": "Designated smoking areas are available in [specific locations]."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Policies",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What are the penalties for smoking in non-smoking areas?",
        "Sample Answer": "Penalties for smoking in non-smoking areas may include fines or charges for cleaning fees."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Policies",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there any rooms specifically designated for smokers?",
        "Sample Answer": "No, we do not have rooms specifically designated for smokers. Our hotel has a no smoking policy"
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Policies",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Is there a smoking fee if I smoke in a non-smoking room?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, there is a smoking fee for smoking in a non-smoking room."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Policies",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Na",
        "Question": "Can I smoke on the balcony or terrace of my room?",
        "Sample Answer": "Smoking is allowed only on the balcony or terrace of your room."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Policies",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are electronic cigarettes allowed in the hotel?",
        "Sample Answer": "No, electronic cigarettes are not allowed in the hotel. For health, safety, and cleanliness reasons, we do not permit the use of electronic cigarettes on our premises."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "Requests",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Policies",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What is the hotel's policy on smoking marijuana or other substances?",
        "Sample Answer": "The hotel strictly prohibits smoking marijuana or other substances on the premises."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Policies",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Policies",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there any outdoor areas where smoking is prohibited?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, smoking is prohibited in all indoor and outdoor areas except for designated smoking areas."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "What spa services do you offer?",
        "Sample Answer": "We offer massages, facials, body treatments, and more."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "How much does a massage session cost?",
        "Sample Answer": "Massage sessions start at (rate) for (no) minutes."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Do you provide facials as part of your spa services?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we provide a variety of facials tailored to your skin's needs."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Time frame",
        "Question": "Are there any discounts available for spa packages?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we offer discounts on select spa packages."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "Confirmations",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Na",
        "Question": "Can I book a spa appointment for tomorrow morning?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, you can book a spa appointment for tomorrow morning, subject to availability."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Do you offer couples massages?",
        "Sample Answer": "Yes, we offer couples massages for a romantic experience."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "Na",
        "Question": "What type of massages do your therapists specialize in?",
        "Sample Answer": "Our therapists specialize in Swedish, deep tissue, hot stone, and aromatherapy massages."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "Are there any additional amenities included with spa services?",
        "Sample Answer": "Additional amenities include access to our sauna, steam room, and relaxation areas."
    },
    {
        "Category": "Amenities",
        "Sub Category": "FAQs",
        "Sub Sub Category": "Services",
        "Information Required From Client ": "NA",
        "Question": "How far in advance do I need to book a spa appointment?",
        "Sample Answer": "We recommend booking your spa appointment at least 8 hours in advance."
    }
]